(Leonard:)I know you guys don't want to do this,
but we have no choice.
(Leonard:)You can either bitch and whine
or we can get it over with.
- I got whine.
- I got the B-word.
(Leonard:)Yeah, well, it's in our contract
to serve on a university committee.
(Leonard:)And frankly,
this is one I believe in, okay? Here:
(Leonard:)Encouraging more women
to pursue a career in the sciences.
Come on, if I was good
at convincing women to do stuff...
(Howard:)...I wouldn't have spent
so much of my 20's in the shower. Heh.
(Sheldon:)If you ask me,
this whole thing is a waste of our time.
- Helping women?
- Yeah, helping anyone.
(Sheldon:)People should take care of themselves.
(Leonard:)Oh, like yesterday when you
made me drive you to the dry cleaners...
(Leonard:)...the pharmacy and the post office?
(Sheldon:)I'm not saying people can't use tools.
(Sheldon:)Even an otter picks up a rock
when he wants a clam.
You don't think it's worthwhile to get
more women in science?
(Sheldon:)I think that's incredibly sexist of you.
(Sheldon:)I believe in a gender-blind society
like in Star Trek...